Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- China College Files, Series IV
  - Nanking, University of
    - Correspondence
      - Gamble, D. B., 1916-1919 (Box 213, Folder 3623)
      - Garritt, J. C., 1918-1923 (Box 213, Folder 3623)
      - Ginling College, 1916-1919 (Box 213, Folder 3623)
      - Gless, Bertha M., 1924-1928 (Box 213, Folder 3624)
      - Goucher, John F., 1918-1919 (Box 213, Folder 3625)
      - Gray, Alfred V., 1919 (Box 213, Folder 3625)
      - Griffing, Burgoyne, 1923-1934 (Box 213, Folder 3626)
      - Griffing, John B., 1919-1929 (Box 213, Folder 3626)
      - Hall Estate, 1924-1929 (Box 213, Folder 3627)
      - Hamilton, Clarence H., 1927-1931 (Box 214, Folder 3628)
      - Hammargren Bequest, 1935 (Box 214, Folder 3628)
      - Hancock, M. Leslie, 1921-1927 (Box 214, Folder 3629)
      - Harbison Estate, 1922 (Box 214, Folder 3630)
      - Harkness, Edward S., 1914-1924 (Box 214, Folder 3630)
      - Harper, F.A., 1933 (Box 214, Folder 3630)
      - Harvard-Yenching Institute, 1929-1945 (Box 214, Folder 3631-3635)
      - Hayes, Herbert, 1936 (Box 214, Folder 3636)
      - Hickok, Paul, 1922-1924 (Box 214, Folder 3637)
      - Higgins, Margaret, 1932 (Box 214, Folder 3638)
      - Hiltner, Walter G., 1916 (Box 214, Folder 3638)
      - Holgate, Thomas, 1912, 1921-1924 (Box 214, Folder 3638)
      - Holroyd, Ben, 1925-1927 (Box 214, Folder 3638)
      - Hoover Trust, 1927-1936 (Box 214, Folder 3639)
      - Horne, Frank A., 1916-1927 (Box 214, Folder 3639)
      - Horton, Etta, 1927 (Box 214, Folder 3640)
      - Hume, Edward H., 1929 (Box 214, Folder 3640)
      - Hummel, W. F., 1924, 1927 (Box 214, Folder 3640)
      - Hund, Ella, 1923-1927 (Box 214, Folder 3640)
      - Hutcheson, Allen C., 1918-1929 (Box 214, Folder 3641)
      - Hutcheson, Joseph C., 1927 (Box 214, Folder 3642)
      - Hynds, Iva, 1925-1936 (Box 214, Folder 3642)
      - Illick, J. Theron, 1922-1942 (Box 214, Folder 3643)
      - Institute for Research in Land Economics and Public Utilities, 1919-1930 (Box 215, Folder 3644)
      - Institute of Pacific Relations (Box 215, Folder 3644a)
      - International Education Board, 1926-1932 (Box 215, Folder 3645)
      - Jeffrey, Margaret, 1928-1934 (Box 215, Folder 3645)
      - Jessup, Mrs. Morris K., 1913 (Box 215, Folder 3646)
      - Jones, Ernest V., 1927-1930 (Box 215, Folder 3646)
      - Joy, James R., 1916 (Box 215, Folder 3646)
      - Keen, Charles S., 1914-1927 (Box 215, Folder 3647)
      - Keen Memorial Collection
      - Kees, Margaret C., 1941-1942 (Box 215, Folder 3648)
      - Keigwin, Edwin A., 1922-1924 (Box 215, Folder 3648)
      - Kennedy, David S., 1922-1923 (Box 215, Folder 3649)
      - King, Mr. and Mrs. Ogden, 1934-1936 (Box 215, Folder 3649)
      - Kuo, Mr. and Mrs. T. S., 1929 (Box 215, Folder 3649)
      - Lane, E.W., 1916 (Box 215, Folder 3650)
      - Lasell, Sidney L., 1916-1919 (Box 215, Folder 3650)
      - Levering, Joshua, 1916 (Box 215, Folder 3650)
      - Lewis, Ardron, 1933 (Box 215, Folder 3650)
      - Li, S. Y., 1924 (Box 215, Folder 3651)
      - Liang, H.S., 1924 (Box 215, Folder 3651)
      - Lin, D. Y., 1918-1919 (Box 215, Folder 3651)
      - Liu, K. C., 1922-1927 (Box 215, Folder 3652)
      - Liu, Kuang-Pei, 1924 (Box 215, Folder 3652)
      - Liu, N. C., 1924 (Box 215, Folder 3652)
      - Lobenstine, Edwin C., 1916-1936 (Box 215, Folder 3653)
      - Love, H. H., 1924-1935 (Box 215, Folder 3654)
      - Lowdermilk, Mr. and Mrs. Walter, 1922-1930 (Box 215, Folder 3655)
      - Ludlow Peabody, Architects, 1912 (Box 215, Folder 3656)
      - Lusk, Ellen M., 1924 (Box 215, Folder 3656)
      - McCormick, Mrs. Cyrus, 1915-1919 (Box 215, Folder 3656)
      - McCormick, Cyrus, Jr., 1927 (Box 215, Folder 3656)
      - Macklin, Theodore and William, 1919 (Box 215, Folder 3656)
      - Maynard, L. A., 1933-1934 (Box 215, Folder 3657)
      - Mertsky, Grace C., 1929-1930 (Box 215, Folder 3658)
      - Methodist Church, Board of Missions and Church Extension (See also: Methodist Episcopal Church), 1941-1945 (Box 216, Folder 3659)
      - Methodist Episcopal Church, Board of Foreign Missions, 1907-1924 (Box 216, Folder 3660-3674)
      - Middleton, Gordon K., 1929-1930 (Box 217, Folder 3675)
      - Milbank Memorial Fund, 1933-1934 (Box 217, Folder 3675)
      - Mills, Samuel G., 1923-1936 (Box 217, Folder 3676)
      - Millward, William, 1916 (Box 217, Folder 3677)
      - Montgomery, R.P., 1914 (Box 217, Folder 3677)
      - Morrow, Dwight W., 1927 (Box 217, Folder 3677)
      - Moss, Leslie B., 1918-1924 (Box 217, Folder 3678)
      - Mott, John R., 1916 (Box 217, Folder 3679)
      - Munn, Jane, 1926-1928 (Box 217, Folder 3679)
      - Myers, C.H., 1925-1935 (Box 217, Folder 3680, 3681)
      - Nanking Theological Seminary, 1916-1935 (Box 217, Folder 3682)
      - New York State Department of Education, 1911-1941 (Box 217, Folder 3683-3688)
      - Newark Museum Association, 1923 (Box 217, Folder 3689)
      - Ni, Tsing-Yuan, 1935-1936 (Box 217, Folder 3689)
      - North, Eric, 1923-1932 (Box 217, Folder 3689)
      - Otto, Earl, 1929-1930 (Box 217, Folder 3690)
      - Owen, Lewis H., 1916-1928 (Box 218, Folder 3691-3699)
      - Partridge, Franklin L., 1929-1932 (Box 218, Folder 3700)
      - Paul, Charles T., 1916 (Box 218, Folder 3700)
      - Peddie School, 1924 (Box 218, Folder 3700)
      - Peden, E.A., 1923-1924 (Box 218, Folder 3701)
      - Perkins, Fellows Hamilton, Architects, 1913-1927 (Box 218, Folder 3702)
      - Re. Personal property losses in looting of Nanking, 1927 (Box 218, Folder 3703)
      - Pierce, Thirza, 1919-1920 (Box 218, Folder 3704)
      - Porter, Rupert H., 1916-1928 (Box 218, Folder 3705, 3706)
      - Presbyterian Church in the United States, Executive Committee fo Foreign Missions, 1912-1930 (Box 219, Folder 3707, 3708)
      - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Board of Foreign Missions, 1910-1924 (Box 219, Folder 3709-3721)
      - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Board of Foreign Missions, 1925-1945 (Box 220, Folder 3722-3730)
      - Price, Frank W., 1928-1931 (Box 220, Folder 3731)
      - Price, P. Frank, 1919 (Box 220, Folder 3731)
      - Priest, Elsie, 1926-1929 (Box 220, Folder 3732-3736)
      - Priest, Elsie, 1930-1936 (Box 221, Folder 3737-3749)
      - Priest, Elsie, 1937-1944 (Box 222, Folder 3750-3763)
      - Priest, Elsie, 1945 (Box 223, Folder 3764)
      - Pritchard, A. B., 1914 (Box 223, Folder 3765)
      - Protestant Episcopal Church, 1922-1930 (Box 223, Folder 3765)
      - Purcell, Minnie H., 1927-1936 (Box 223, Folder 3766)
      - Raeburn, John, 1936 (Box 223, Folder 3767)
      - Reformed Church in the United States, 1922-1930 (Box 223, Folder 3767)
      - Reisner, John H., 1914-1927 (Box 223, Folder 3768-3779)
      - Reisner, John H., 1928-1934 (Box 224, Folder 3780-3785)
      - Rice, Edward L., 1925 (Box 224, Folder 3786)
      - Riggs, Charles and Grace, 1932-1940 (Box 224, Folder 3787, 3788)
      - Riley, W.A., 1924-1925 (Box 224, Folder 3789)
      - Ritchey, George E., 1919-1927 (Box 224, Folder 3789)
      - Robson, Horace G., 1927-1932 (Box 224, Folder 3790)
      - Rockefeller Foundation (See also: China Medical Board), 1921-1935 (Box 224, Folder 3791)
      - Roys, Harvey C., 1918 (Box 224, Folder 3792)
      - Russell, H.L., 1929 (Box 224, Folder 3792)
      - Russell, Victoria F., 1924-1927 (Box 224, Folder 3792)
      - Sage Legacy, 1921-1922 (Box 224, Folder 3793)
      - Sarvis, Guy W., 1918-1927 (Box 224, Folder 3794, 3795)
      - Seventh Day Adventists, General Conference, 1930 (Box 224, Folder 3796)
      - Severance, John L., 1913-1936 (Box 224, Folder 3797-3799)
      - Severance, L.H., 1911-1913 (Box 225, Folder 3800)
      - Shanghai Commercial and Savings Bank, 1933 (Box 225, Folder 3801)
      - Shaw, Charles F., 1929-1931 (Box 225, Folder 3801)
      - Shen, S. T., 1932 (Box 225, Folder 3801)
      - Shen, T. H., 1933 (Box 225, Folder 3801)
      - Sherwin, Henry; Sherwin Fund, 1914-1922 (Box 225, Folder 3802)
      - Shields, Randolph T., 1912-1918 (Box 225, Folder 3803)
      - Sie, Harry H., 1934 (Box 225, Folder 3804)
      - Sie, William Kia-Shen, 1916, 1931-1932 (Box 225, Folder 3804)
      - Silk Association of America, 1922-1923 (Box 225, Folder 3805)
      - Skidmore, Lemuel, 1910-1912 (Box 225, Folder 3805)
      - Sloan, T. Dwight, 1918-1927 (Box 225, Folder 3806-3808)
      - Slocum, Burl and Esther, 1934-1941 (Box 225, Folder 3809)
      - Small, Alexander G., 1916-1924, 1927 (Box 225, Folder 3810-3813)
      - Smith, Bertha C., 1922 (Box 225, Folder 3814)
      - Smith, C. Stanley, 1922-1924 (Box 225, Folder 3814)
      - Smythe, Lewis, 1934-1945 (Box 225, Folder 3815)
      - Southern Baptist Convention, Foreign Mission Board, 1912-1924 (Box 225, Folder 3816)
      - Special gifts, 1912-1930 (Box 225, Folder 3817)
      - Speer, James M., Jr., 1925-1930 (Box 225, Folder 3817)
      - Speers, Theodore C., 1936 (Box 225, Folder 3817)
      - Stevens, W. Mackenzie, 1934 (Box 225, Folder 3818)
      - Steward, Albert N., 1920-1942 (Box 226, Folder 3819)
      - Stuart, Anna Golden, 1925-1926 (Box 226, Folder 3820)
      - Stuart, J. Leighton, 1918, 1919, 1930 (Box 226, Folder 3821)
      - Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions, 1918, 1930 (Box 226, Folder 3822)
      - Suvoong, Thomas H. (H. S. Su), 1925 (Box 226, Folder 3822)
      - Swasey, Ambrose, 1912-1936 (Box 226, Folder 3823-3825)
      - Swen Ming-ching, 1940-1945 (Box 226, Folder 3826-3828)
      - Swingle, Walter T., 1919-1932 (Box 226, Folder 3829)
      - Tao Wen-tsing, 1915-1916 (Box 226, Folder 3830)
      - Tappert, Esther E., 1932-1933 (Box 226, Folder 3830)
      - Taylor, Grace, 1918-1919 (Box 226, Folder 3830)
      - Teachers Insurance and Annuities Association of America, 1926-1931 (Box 226, Folder 3831)
      - Teachout, David W., 1916-1925 (Box 226, Folder 3831)
      - Thompson, Warren S., 1929-1930 (Box 226, Folder 3832)
      - Thomson, Claude, 1917-1945 (Box 226, Folder 3832)
      - Thomson, Margaret, 1945 (Box 226, Folder 3832)
      - Tisinger, R.M., 1930 (Box 226, Folder 3833)
      - Treadway, Annie W. (Mrs. Lyman), 1924 (Box 226, Folder 3833)
      - Trimmer, Clifford S., 1922-1932 (Box 226, Folder 3833)
      - Turner, Mrs. Charles P., 1912 (Box 226, Folder 3834)
      - Turner, Edith, 1934 (Box 226, Folder 3834)
      - Turner, P. Margaret, 1936-1945 (Box 226, Folder 3834)
      - Twinem, Paul and Mary, 1919-1936 (Box 227, Folder 3835)
      - Twiss, Georg R., 1924-1925 (Box 227, Folder 3835)
      - re. Union Medical School, Shanghai, 1921-1922 (Box 227, Folder 3836)
      - United Christian Missionary Society, 1920-1945 (Box 227, Folder 3837-3844)
      - United Evangelical Church, 1922 (Box 227, Folder 3845)
      - United States Department of State, 1928-1937 (Box 227, Folder 3845)
      - United States Treasury Department, 1935 (Box 227, Folder 3845)
      - University Hospital, 1918-1937 (Box 227, Folder 3846)
      - University of Chicago Press, 1930 (Box 227, Folder 3846)
      - re. University seal, 1914-1916 (Box 227, Folder 3846)
      - Van Vliet, Helen G., 1923-1935 (Box 227, Folder 3847)
      - Vaughn, Peirce, 1935 (Box 227, Folder 3847)
      - Wade-Jones, Charles, 1924-1925 (Box 227, Folder 3848)
      - Walker, Elizabeth, 1914-1927 (Box 227, Folder 3848)
      - Wang, Chengting T., 1918-1919 (Box 227, Folder 3848)
      - Warner, Florence, 1926-1929 (Box 227, Folder 3849)
      - Warnshuis, Abbe L., 1928-1930 (Box 227, Folder 3849)
      - Warren, George F., 1931-1936 (Box 227, Folder 3849)
      - Warren, Stanley W., 1931 (Box 227, Folder 3849)
      - Weeks, David, 1931-1932 (Box 227, Folder 3850)
      - Wei, H. R., 1936-1942 (Box 227, Folder 3850)
      - Weigel, Pete, 1918-1919 (Box 227, Folder 3850)
      - Weld, W.E., 1935 (Box 227, Folder 3850)
      - Wesleyan Methodist Missionary Society, 1930 (Box 227, Folder 3850)
      - Wheeler, Rachel, 1916-1927 (Box 227, Folder 3851)
      - Wheeler, W. Reginald, 1918-1937 (Box 228, Folder 3852-3854)
      - Whipple, Maude E., 1926-1934 (Box 228, Folder 3855)
      - Whitman, Walter G., 1925 (Box 228, Folder 3856)
      - Wiggans, R.G., 1926-1931 (Box 228, Folder 3857)
      - Wilcox, W.F., 1930 (Box 228, Folder 3858)
      - Williams, Faith, 1936 (Box 228, Folder 3858)
      - Williams, John E., 1911-1921 (Box 228, Folder 3859-3866)
      - Williams, John E., 1922-1926 (Box 229, Folder 3867-3871)
      - Williams, Lilian, 1927-1936 (Box 229, Folder 3872)
      - Williams, Mornay, 1918 (Box 229, Folder 3872)
      - Wilson, Marjorie, 1936-1938 (Box 229, Folder 3873)
      - Wilson, Robert O., 1935-1941 (Box 229, Folder 3874-3876)
      - Wilson, Wilbur F., 1910-1936 (Box 229, Folder 3877)
      - Wixon, Adelaide, 1915-1933 (Box 229, Folder 3878)
      - Wood Scholarship Fund, 1923-1924 (Box 229, Folder 3878)
      - Woodbridge, C. Louise, 1925-1926 (Box 229, Folder 3879)
      - Woodworth, C.W., 1918-1919 (Box 229, Folder 3879)
      - Wright, Mildred E., 1921-1925 (Box 229, Folder 3879)
      - Wu Teh-yao, 1940-1942 (Box 229, Folder 3880)
      - Young, John G., 1929-1935 (Box 229, Folder 3881)
      - Y.M.C.A., 1922-1924 (Box 229, Folder 3881)
      - Y.W.C.A., 1922 (Box 229, Folder 3881)
      - Zander, Mabel R., 1921 (Box 229, Folder 3881)
    - Financial records
      - Budgets, 1911-1941, 1948/1949 (Box 230, Folder 3882-3885)
      - Financial statements/treasurer's reports, 1910-1948 (Box 230, Folder 3886-3891)
      - Miscellaneous, 1912-1939,n.d. (Box 231, Folder 3892)
      - Ledgers (2 volumes), 1922-1956 (Box 231, Folder 3893, 3894)
      - Transfer book, 1929-1956 (Box 232, Folder 3895)
      - Municipal bonds, 1926, 1931 (Box 233, Folder 3896)
      - Nanking Realty Corporation Ledger, 1939-1948 (Box 233, Folder 3897)
      - Nanking Realty Corporation: Legal documents and minutes, 1934-1945 (Box 233, Folder 3898)
      - Register of Trust Funds, 1930 (Box 233, Folder 3899)
      - Register of Trust Funds (bound volume) (Box 233, Folder 3900)
    - Periodical publications
      - Agriculture and Forestry Notes, 1923-1941 (Box 234, Folder 3901, 3902)
      - Bulletin on China's Foreign Relations, 1931-1935 (Box 234, Folder 3903, 3904)
      - Class books, 1934, 1935 (Box 234, Folder 3905)
      - Economic Facts (Dept. of Agricultural Economics), 1939, 1943-1946 (Box 235, Folder 3906, 3907)
      - Economic Weekly (Dept. of Agricultural Economics), 1947 (Box 235, Folder 3907a-3909)
      - Film and Radio News, 1942, 1945 (Box 235, Folder 3910)
      - The Nanking Bulletin of Church and Community, 1925 (Box 235, Folder 3911)
      - Nanking Notes and Notices, 1939 (Box 235, Folder 3912)
      - Notes and Notices of the Nanking Union Church and Community, 1940-1941 (Box 235, Folder 3912)
      - Nanking University Magazine, 1909 (Box 235, Folder 3913)
      - University of Nanking Magazine, 1910-1912 (Box 235A, Folder 3913)
      - University of Nanking Magazine, 1913-1922 (Box 235A, Folder 3914, 3915)
      - University of Nanking Magazine, 1923, 1924, 1930 (Box 236, Folder 3916-3918)
      - The Linguist (Dept. of Missionary Training), 1921, 1922 (Box 461, Folder 1)
      - The Linguist (Dept. of Missionary Training), 1923, 1924 (Box 236, Folder 3919)
      - Student handbook, 1924, 1925 (Box 236, Folder 3920)
    - Publicity/reports
      - Brochures and pamphlets, 1910-1958,n.d. (Box 237, Folder 3921-3923)
      - Magazine and newspaper articles, 1911-1938 (Box 237, Folder 3924)
      - Newsletters, memoranda, reports, 1906-1937 (Box 237, Folder 3925-3932)
      - Newsletters, memoranda, reports, 1938-1950,n.d. (Box 238, Folder 3933-3936)
  - St. John's University
    - Administrative
      - St. John's University Committee of the UBCCC, 1948-1951 (Box 239, Folder 3937)
    - Academic
      - Degrees conferred, 1928 (Box 239, Folder 3938)
      - Student enrollment statistics, 1948 (Box 239, Folder 3938)
      - Related to alumni, 1937-1970 (Box 239, Folder 3939)
      - Related to faculty and staff, 1913-1949,n.d. (Box 239, Folder 3940)
      - Re. Medical Department (The Pennsylvania Medical School), 1920, 1935-1950,n.d. (Box 239, Folder 3941)
      - Re. Library and School of Engineering, 1924, 1947,n.d. (Box 239, Folder 3942)
    - Correspondence
      - Pott, Francis Lister Hawks, 1923-1945 (Box 239, Folder 3943)
    - Periodical publications
      - Dragon Flag, 1904, 1907 (Box 239, Folder 3944)
      - The St. John's Echo, 1900-1905 (Box 239, Folder 3945)
    - Publicity/reports
      - Re. St. John's monograph by Mary Lamberton, 1951-1954 (Box 239, Folder 3945a)
      - Miscellaneous, 1935-1950,n.d. (Box 239, Folder 3946)
  - Shanghai, University of
    - Administrative
      - Board of Founders, 1937-1946 (Box 240, Folder 3947)
      - Board of Directors, 1938-1945, 1949 (Box 240, Folder 3948)
      - President's annual reports, 1940, 1941, 1947 (Box 240, Folder 3949)
    - Academic
      - Reports from Dean's Office, 1939-1942 (Box 240, Folder 3950)
      - Catalog, bulletins, 1933, 1939, 1940 (Box 240, Folder 3951)
      - Student enrollment statistics, 1948-1950 (Box 240, Folder 3952)
      - Related to alumni, 1945-1947,n.d. (Box 240, Folder 3953)
      - Related to faculty and administrators, 1938-1954 (Box 240, Folder 3954)
    - Correspondence
      - Chao Kuo-chung, 1945 (Box 240, Folder 3955)
      - Choy, J.K., 1945 (Box 240, Folder 3955)
      - Harris, W.A., 1937 (Box 240, Folder 3955)
      - Hipps, J.B., 1945 (Box 240, Folder 3955)
      - Lin, Henry H., 1944-1948 (Box 240, Folder 3956)
      - Liu, Herman C.E., 1928-1938 (Box 240, Folder 3957, 3958)
      - Liu, Mrs. Herman, 1938 (Box 240, Folder 3959)
      - Robins, Henry B., 1931-1939 (Box 240, Folder 3960)
      - Sears, Minnie S., 1940 (Box 240, Folder 3961)
      - Van Tsing Kong, 1938-1941 (Box 240, Folder 3962, 3963)
      - Westbrook, Charles, 1922 (Box 240, Folder 3962, 3963)
      - White, Frank J., 1923-1943 (Box 240, Folder 3964)
    - Financial records
      - Budgets and statements, 1937-1945, 1949 (Box 240, Folder 3965)
    - Periodical publications
      - Shanghai Spectator, 1947 (Box 240, Folder 3966)
    - Publicity/reports
      - Miscellaneous, 1942-1946 (Box 240, Folder 3967)
  - Shantung Christian University/Cheeloo University
    - Administrative
      - Re. charter and by-laws, 1924 (Box 241, Folder 3968, 3969)
      - Re. charter and by-laws, 1925, 1929, 1936 (Box 241, Folder 3970)
      - Board of Governors: Bound volume of minutes with index, 1919-1928 Sep (Box 241, Folder 3971)
      - Board of Governors: Bound volume of minutes, 1928 Sep-1934 Feb (Box 241, Folder 3972)
      - Board of Governors: Bound voumes of minutes, 1934 Mar-1952 (Box 242, Folder 3973, 3974)
      - Shantung Christian University Committee of the UBCCC/UBCHEA, 1953-1957 (Box 243, Folder 3975)
      - Administrative Council: Minutes, 1928-1935 (Box 243, Folder 3976)
      - Field Board of Managers and Administrative Council: Minutes (See: under Periodical Publications: Shantung Christian University Bulletin (Box 243, Folder 3976)
      - Board of Directors: Minutes, 1930-1946 (Box 243, Folder 3977, 3978)
      - Board of Directors: Advisory Committee, 1941 (Box 243, Folder 3979)
      - Board of Directors: Executive Committee, 1941 (Box 243, Folder 3979)
      - Board of Directors: Women's Committee, 1941 (Box 243, Folder 3979)
      - Senate: Minutes, 1925-1930 (Box 243, Folder 3980)
      - British Joint Board: Constitution and Minutes, 1918-1925 (Box 243, Folder 3981)
      - North American Section, Board of Governors: Constitution, 1919 (Box 243, Folder 3982)
      - North American Section, Board of Governors: Executive Committee, 1928 (Box 243, Folder 3982)
      - North American Section, Board of Governors: Women's Committee, 1933 (Box 243, Folder 3982)
      - President's annual reports, 1936-1947 (Box 243, Folder 3983)
      - Woman's Committee of the North American Section of the Board of Governors, 1930-1941 (Box 243, Folder 3984)
      - President's Committee for Women Students, 1941 (Box 243, Folder 3985)
      - Cheeloo School of Theology Board of Directors, and Emergency Committee, 1930-1937, 1946 (Box 243, Folder 3986)
      - School of Medicine Woman's Committee: By-laws, minutes, correspondence, 1924-1941 (Box 243, Folder 3987)
      - Medical Faculty Meetings: Minutes, 1928-1938 (Box 243, Folder 3988)
      - Conference on Shantung Christian University: Minutes, 1917, 1918 (Box 243, Folder 3989)
      - Property leases, 1933-1935,n.d. (Box 243, Folder 3990)
      - Blueprints, map (See also: Oversize material), 1927,n.d. (Box 243, Folder 3991)
    - Academic (see also: under Periodical Publications: Shantung Christian University Bulletins )
      - Catalogue of Tengchow College, 1891 (Box 244, Folder 3992)
      - Dean of Women: Reports, 1926-1939, 1944 (Box 244, Folder 3993)
      - Student enrollment records, 1920-1941, 1948 (Box 244, Folder 3994)
      - Related to alumni, 1928-1970 (Box 244, Folder 3995)
      - Related to faculty and staff: Misc., 1927-1950 (Box 244, Folder 3996)
      - Related to faculty and staff: Publications: Balme, Harold, 1925-1928 (Box 244, Folder 3997)
      - Related to faculty and staff: Publications: Hsi En Wang, 1928 (Box 244, Folder 3997)
      - Related to faculty and staff: Publications: Shields, R. T. re. medical missions in China, 1929-1944 (Box 244, Folder 3998)
      - Related to faculty and staff: Publications: Russell, Mary K. (Box 244, Folder 3999)
      - Related to faculty and staff: Publications: Williamson, H. R., 1928 (Box 244, Folder 3999)
      - Agricultural Sanitation Investigation, 1939, 1941 (Box 244, Folder 4000)
      - Child welfare work, 1930-1932 (Box 244, Folder 4001)
      - Department of sociology, 1924 (Box 244, Folder 4002)
      - Harvard-Yenching Institute, 1929-1935 (Box 244, Folder 4003)
      - Sinological Research Institute, 1947 (Box 244, Folder 4003)
      - Rural Institute, Tsinan Institute, Extension Department, 1924-1942, 1946 (Box 244, Folder 4004)
      - School of Arts and Science, 1924-1934 (Box 244, Folder 4005)
      - School of Medicine: Alumni lists and statistics, 1890-1943 (Box 245, Folder 4006)
      - School of Medicine: Reports, 1915-1947,n.d. (Box 245, Folder 4007-4012)
      - (See also: under Periodical Publications: Shantung Christian University Bulletins )
      - School of Medicine: Material related to vivisection, 1934-1936 (Box 246, Folder 4013)
      - College for Medicine, Foochow, 1948, 1949 (Box 246, Folder 4014)
      - School of Theology, 1923-1946 (Box 246, Folder 4015, 4016)
      - Sinological Research Institute, 1937-1945 (Box 246, Folder 4017)
      - Tsinan Leper Hospital, 1931, 1932 (Box 246, Folder 4018)
      - University Hospital: Reports, 1915-1947,n.d. (Box 246, Folder 4019, 4020)
      - University Hospital: Reports, 1934-1947 (Box 247, Folder 4021-4023)
      - University Hospital: Organization, 1929-1941 (Box 247, Folder 4024)
      - University Hospital: Staff and salaries, 1939, 1941,n.d. (Box 247, Folder 4025)
      - University Middle School: Report, 1928 (Box 247, Folder 4026)
      - Miscellaneous, 1924-1940 (Box 247, Folder 4027)
    - Correspondence
      - Abbott, Paul, 1921-1934 (Box 248, Folder 4028)
      - Adolph, William H., 1921-1934 (Box 248, Folder 4028)
      - American Baptist Foreign Mission Society, 1918-1920 (Box 248, Folder 4028)
      - American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions, 1918-1936 (Box 248, Folder 4029)
      - American Medical Association, 1928 (Box 248, Folder 4030)
      - Armitage, Auriol, 1920 (Box 248, Folder 4030)
      - Balme, Harold, 1916-1924 Jun (Box 248, Folder 4031-4037)
      - Balme, Harold, 1924 Jul-1933 (Box 249, Folder 4038-4041)
      - Bergen, Paul D., 1902-1904 (Box 249, Folder 4042)